<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<CLAUSE DESC="ADVP_EN_STD" ID="C00000000112" MODULE="GTEE" NAME="ADVP_EN_STD" PREFIX="[[[" SUFFIX="]]]" AutoGen-Parameter-Version="1.0">
    <value><![CDATA[We have been informed that the Applicant has entered into the Contract with you.  
Furthermore, we understand that, according to the conditions of the Contract, an advance payment in the amount of [[[GTEE_CCY]]][[[GTEE_AMT]]], representing [[[X798_37J_GURE_VALUE_PERCENT]]] PCT of the amount of the Contract, is to be made against an advance payment guarantee.
As guarantor we, CSBANK, hereby irrevocably undertake to pay you any amount not exceeding in total the Guarantee Amount upon receipt by us of your demand in writing including your statement in what respect the Applicant is in breach of its obligation(s) under the Contract.
It is a condition for any claim and payment under this guarantee to be made that the advance payment referred to above must have been received by the Applicant. A demand under this guarantee must include a statement by your bank, stating that the said bank has paid the advance payment referred to above to the Applicants account number, referring to this guarantee.
This guarantee is not assignable or transferable without our and Applicants prior written consent.
Any demand for payment under this guarantee must be received by us in writing by registered mail at this office on or before the Expiry Date. The original of this guarantee shall be returned to us upon expiry. However, after our payment of the whole of the Guarantee Amount or the Expiry Date, whichever comes first, this guarantee will become null and void, whether returned to us or not.
For the purpose of identification, your request for payment in writing must be presented to us through the intermediary of a first rate bank confirming that the signatures thereon are legally binding upon you.
Your claim is also acceptable if transmitted to us in full by duly encoded SWIFT through a first rate bank confirming that your original claim has been sent to us by registered airmail and that the signatures thereon are legally binding upon you.  
Your claim will be considered as having been made once we are in possession of the written request for payment or SWIFT to this effect at our address. If claimed by SWIFT, the original written claim must be submitted to us.
]]></value>
</CLAUSE>